The Reverse Cowgirl S16E01
Subtitles: NL-Subs Darkone
Throw it here!
Yeah!
Nice one, Clyde!
Clyde!
Clyde, get up here!
Hurry!
What is that?
A toilet.
That's right.
It's a toilet, Clyde.
And where is the toilet seat?
It's up.
Because you left it up.
Again!
We've been through this a countless times, Clyde.
Okay mom, just not in front of my friends okay?
No, not okay. Because you
aren't getting the message!
What if I'd fallen in?
Start listening to me!
Put it down!
Thank you.
Dude, that sucks, Clyde.
A mom shouldn't be able to put
rules on toilet-time like that.
Toilet-time is the last
bastion of American freedom.
Is your mom always like that, dude?
Look, could you guys...
not say anything about
this in school, please?
Ofcourse man.
It's cool.
Clyde, Clyde!
What have I told you
about pissing on the seat?
and Clyde's all like...
Okay mom, fuck! Not in
front of my friends!
Cartman, it was actually really lame.
I know, right!
Women are just jealous 'cause they
have to face outwards to pee and crap.
Clyde!
Aah, there you are!
Mom?
Clyde Donovan, you come
home this instant!
Why?
What have I told you about...
putting the toiletseat down
after you go to the bathroom?
Mom, I'm in class.
How many times do I
have to tell you, Clyde?
I was trying to get ready for work
and the toilet seat was up, again.
Betsy, come back home,
it's just not that big a deal.
No, Roger. It's a disgusting habit
and I'm sick and tired of it.
If I had sat down, I would have
gotten toilet water all over my vagina.
My grandma is
from Virginia.
You're coming home right now, and
you're putting the seat where it belongs.
Dude, I'm telling you it
was freaking hysterical.
Clyde had to get up in middle of class and
follow his mom home to put the seat down.
He was so embarrassed, dude, I
thought he was gonna die.
I know, fat-ass.
I was there.
His mom...
His mom goes
Clyde, you're an asshole and now
I have toilet water in my vagigi.
That's not what she said.
You're putting extra's on it again.
It's not that funny.
I know dude. The bathroom is the
last bastion of American freedoom.
Don't you feel just a
little bad for Clyde?
Uh uh.
Well you should.
The poor guy shouldn't be screamed at
for something that isn't that big a deal at all.
What's going on?
They're trying to save Clydes mom.
From what?
They're saying Clyde left
the toilet seat up again.
Hang in there. You're going to
be fine okay? Stay with me now.
I'm sorry, there's nothing we can do.
What?!
When she fell into the toilet,
she also made it flush.
It created a suction that's literally
pulling out her insides.
Can't we disconnect the
toilet from the plumbing?
Yes, we'll have to, but
when we do that the change in
pressure will rip out her organs.
But she's not going to die, is she?
Why did you leave the
toilet seat up, son?
Clyde!
I want you to know that I
don't blame you for this.
We should've been
harder on you all those times
you left the toilet seat up.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I...don't...
have a lot of time, Clyde.
Just...
please...
put the seat down
from now on.
for your sisters sake, please.
Oh, God, please let me go.
Let me go.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Mom?
I'll always remember Betsy Donovans
kind nature, more then anything.
She always treated people
with dignity and respect.
What a tradegy she had
to leave us so soon.
But I'm sure Betsy is hoping that
her dead will help women everywhere
just take that extra second to
look before they sit on a toilet.
I'd like to say on
behalf of the departed, that
it isn't a womens responsibility
to see that the seat is down.
It's a mens responsibility
to put it down.
It's not that hard.
Yeah, yes. That's right.
Putting the toilet seat
down isn't that hard.
So is it too much too
ask women to just look?
And put it down before they go plopping
their butts blindly to the toilet bowl?
My God, people. This is a funeral!
Please have some respect!
There is a little boy here
who has lost his mother!
He'll never see her again!
Because he couldn't take that sixth-
tenth of a second to put the seat down
when he was done peeing.
And now little Clyde's mother is dead.
And the blood is on his penis.
It's too bad we didn't find any
treasure on the subway, Phillip.
Hi Ugly Bob. Hi Terrance, hi Phillip.
Mom, get the door!
You're looking hideously
ugly today, Ugly Bob.
How come you guys sayt stuff like that?
Because you're goddamn ugly...
Hello mam, we're the toilet
safety administration.
The what?
After the recent tragedy, new safety
regulations require us to check all toilets.
Can we come in?
Sure.
Who are these buttholes?
It's the toilet
safety administration, hun.
They're going to do
something to the potty.
My potty? What are
they going to do to it?
He, he!
That's my bathroom.
Oh yeah, we're going to have
to completely redo this mam.
You need to have this counter
moved a minimum of six inches
But we'll go ahead and install
your safety belt. --Safety belt?
Federal law requires all toilets to be
fitted with a harnes so nobody can fall in.
Dude, you can't make me wear
a seatbelt to take a dump.
This is for your safety.
A woman died, you know.
Yeah, but the bloods on
Clyde's weiner, not mine.
Sir, we are really worried
about our friend Clyde.
Everywhere he goes people
are telling him he has blood
on his weiner.
Uh-uh, go on.
We keep trying to tell him
maybe this all isn't his fault.
Maybe the people who made the toilet
are to blame for what happened.
So we were just wondering...
if we could sue somebody.
You can always sue somebody.
All right, you see, Clyde.
Okay, we wanna help him sue
whoever invented the toilet.
You got it.
Here we go,
the inventor of the toilet.
Sir Thomas Harrington.
In England, died in 1692.
Aw, he's dead?
So, then we can't sue him?
Why not? You can
always sue somebody.
Just going to take
some special protocol.
We would have to perform...
a suance.
A...a...a...a...
suance?
You bet.
Here at Hoffman and Turk we
specialize in suing the dead.
If you hire us,
we'll work hard...
for you.
Wow, really?!
You hear that, Clyde?
Now look,
I'll be asking all of you
to have a very open mind
and a willingness to
face your fears.
I warn you boys.
A suance can be very...
expensive.
How expensive?
How much do you have?
Clyde got $3000 from
his moms life insurrance.
Wow!
That's exactly how
much a suance costs.
Wow, that's weird.
Damn it!
He, he, officer.
If you're sitting on the toilet you
need to wear your safety belt, sir.
Yeah, I know, I had it on.
I just took it of for a second
to get the uh... to get...
The address here is 260
avenue de los Mexicanos?
Ooh, come on, don't
give me a ticket!
Got to wear the safety belt
or you could fall in.
I'm nog going to fall in.
I'm not a chick.
The law is the law, sir.
You can pay this by
mail or appear in court on that date.
Have a good day, sir.
Yeah, thanks.
Asshole.
You say something?
No, I was talking
to my asshole.
Come on, asshole.
Let get back to work.
This is unbelievable.
Stupid toilet
safety administration.
You can't even take a crap at IHOP
without a fourty-minute line!
Shoes off, belts off!
Sharp objects go in the plastic tray!
This is inhumane.
Shut up!
Sir.
Taking a dump today, mam?
No, just need to pee.
I'll just need to check
inside your asshole.
Hee, how about you people
speed it up in here?
I'm about to crap my pants and
I demand access to the toilets
right now!
Do you mind if I toch
your balls, sir?
What? Yes I'd mind!
Do you mind if I touch
your fucking balls?
Okay, I'm done.
Right, sir. I just need to
check inside your asshole.
I don't need you wiping my ass
for me. I am a grown man.
Yes, you're a big boy, aren't you, sir?
Yeah, I'm a big boy.
That's a big boy, sir.
I'm a big boy.
I took a big boy poop.
Yes.
Alright boys, sit down
and clear your minds.
The suance is
about to begin.
Doors and windows are locked.
You boys have your $500 in cash ready?
Yeah.
Alright. Then I've got this big bowl set
here, to catch all money were about to make.
Now. Let us start.
We call out to the
land of the dead.
Sir John Harrington
Your presence is requested.
Appear to us, John Harrington.
We have a subpoena.
Jeez, it's not working.
John Harrington.
My client is due
compensation for negligence.
What is your name, spirit?
Burns.
Jimmy Burns.
What's it to you?
Who are you, mugs?
That's how people
talked in the past.
We have a claim against a John
Harrington. Do you know him spirit?
Well, maybe I do
and maybe I don't.
Might need a little something
something to jar my memory.
We got to grease him.
Put a hundred in the box.
Oh yeah, Harrington.
I know him.
Always going round
inventing things.
Yes, that's him. Is his
personage amongst you?
Well, maybe it is
and maybe it isn't.
Give him another hundred.
Yeah, I've seen
him around, alright.
He was just down that way. Bragging
about some porcelain machine.
No!
By the power of Christ,
we sue you.
You can't sue me!
Quick, put the other
$300 in the box!
This actualy went really, really well.
Always happens some burocrate tries
to block the first sue ons attempt.
But this was good.
We'll get him tomorrow.
So, that's it?
Yeah, were going to need
about 400 more dollars tomorrow.
I know you're sad about your mom, Clyde.
But don't worry. We're going to win this thing.
Put your coffee in the
plastic tray, please, sir.
Shoes off. Belts off.
Yeah, yeah.
Got any metal
in your pockets?
I just need to
check your asshole.
So ridiculous.
Asshole clear.
Thanks.
Pick your coffee up, sir.
Anyways, he says i'm getting
nothing anyway, so you can...
Hee, what's that thing?
That's a camera.
It's a security camera.
You people have me on camera now?
It's okay sir. There's
just one person
viewing the monitors
in a discrete location.
How long are we
going to sit around
while our freedoms are
stripped away one by one.
Time for us to stand together and say,
we want the goverment out of our bathrooms.
Now listen.
All we have to do is
agree as a community
to all bolt our
toilet seats down.
If they can't raise or lower,
there's zero change of anyone falling in.
If there's no toilet seats, the
goverment can't make toilet seat laws.
No, no. hold on.
If the seat can't raise up the
men will just pee all over it.
No, we won't.
Yeah, you will.
Well, sorry if women might have to deal
with a little splash of pee on the rimm.
But its a far beter solution then
having the goverment in our batrooms, right?
How about we agree
to that, if...
men will agree that they will
always sit down to urinate.
Well, no, you can't make
men sit down to pee.
How could we play
sink the boat?
Yeah, how will Nelson and I
make an X on sleepover nights?
What about us loggers?
Hardworking men who like to stand up
after they have taken a poo
and then turn around and cut
their poo in half with their urine?
Sorry, but if we don't want the
goverment treating us like children,
we might have to give up being
able to pee our feces in half.
But folks been logging round
these parts for generations.
My papy taught me logging.
And his papy before him.
Yeah, I think we just
got to live with the TSA.
Yeah, yeah.
Merciful summary on
behalf of the plaintive?
What's happening now?
Our motion has been
denied by the judge.
Concentrate boys!
This Spectre is like none
I have ever encountered.
He managed to avert liability
within injunction against our claim.
So, what does that mean?
We'll hit him with a
class-action lawsuit tomorrow.
We'll need all your friends and family
to sign a petition and kick in 50 bucks each.
What?!
Hang in there, Clyde. This is all
to make the world a safer place.
Security breach!
An embarrassing day for the
toilets safety administration.
Shocking outrage ensued
after an unknown terrorist
managed to get through TSA
security with a gun and a baby.
Leaving the toilet seat up.
The head of TSA chief of
operations had this to say;
Shit!
Meanwhile, outraged civilians
claiming they're finally fed up
with the overblown
goverment bureaucracy.
What good is the TSA if
they're not protecting us?
Why have we given up freedom if terrorists
can take a hostage in a bathroom...
with a baby and a gun
on the toilet?
And the toilet seat was up.
We've all stood by as mother
goverment is taking our dignity.
That's right!
Now it is time to take
responsibility for ourselves.
It is time for all
of us to grow up.
That's right.
It is time
for a suance.
Wait, what?
What the fuck
is a suance?
Tom, I'm standing outside
the South Park courthouse
where experts have succesfully
summoned the ghost
of toilet inventor
sir John Harrington.
Now that the spirit has
crossed over from the dead.
lawyers are going to
try and sue him.
Sir Thomas Harrington, your extreme
negliglence has cost tax payers millions.
No!
You will be sooth, spirtit.
Thy liability is without question.
Appear before this
court, Harrington.
Never!
Quick, everyone, get
out all your money.
Clyde?
Mom?
This lawyer is a fraud.
He has been swindeling you and
your friends for your money.
Fuck me, it's a ghost.
You can't sue the dead, Clyde.
Putting the toilet seat down
is a matter of simple etiquette.
It's common sense, Clyde.
Oh boy, here we go.
Don't try and blame mommies death
on anything but your faillure.
to do something I have asked
you time and time again to do.
It's your fault.
Now hold on just a second!
It's not anyone's fault.
I'am sick and tired of all this nonsense
over my porcelain toilet machine.
There he is.
Sir John Harrington.
Quick, sue him!
You can't sue me.
You're all using my toilet
invention the wrong way.
When you have to sit and
take a sir Harrington...
you're suppoosed to
be facing this way.
So you can use the little shelf for
your books, and your quill and your ink.
Aha!
I told you you should sit
on it that way! I told you!
Why would I design it so that when
you're finished taking a sir Harrington
you have to stand up, turn around a look
right down at your Harrington to flush.
That's gross.
Yes, but...
But if you sit on it that way, you have
to take your pants all the way off.
Why do you think I designed
toilet rooms with a laundry hole?
That's what that
hole is for?
Oops.
So then... so then Clydes
moms ghost was all like
Clyde, what have I told
you Clyde, you asshole!
And Clyde is all like
Mom leave me alone!
I'm seriously. Stop, please!
Dude, it was a riot.
That's not what I said.
Yeah, well...
I'm just glad that
stupid TSA crap is over.
I know you've had a tough week, Clyde.
But at least your mom didn't die for nothing.
I mean...
We're kinda right back at to the bathroom
being the last bastion of American freedom
so, technically your mom
did die for nothing, but...
Clyde?
Clyde, you there?
Hello?
Subtitles: NL-Subs Darkone