Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
I know the people are going to
say you should only practice
this way or that way.
I believe in capitalism too.
I believe in capitalism for everybody.
What he said, which I find mildly amazing,
was he thought I would have a
hard time debating Barack Obama.
We faced something greater
after world war ii.
We had ten million coming home at once.
What did we do then?
Some liberals said we need
more work programs --
Tango, Tango in position.
Copy, tango.
Clear vantage point.
Will have to do. We're not getting closer.
Alright, butters. Bring it in.
***, ten seconds.
Copy that.
10 seconds, Carlton.
I can hear that, tell me when to go.
We might have a problem.
What's that?
We just got word somebody might
try to faith hill this event.
Lock down the perimeter.
Nobody is faith hilling not on my watch.
They're onto us guys. Let's do this.
I got it.
Hey, somebody is under the stage.
Go Cartman.
We got it.
Go, go, go.
That was sweet.
First, there was planking.
People taking pictures of
themselves in a planked position
and putting the photos on the Internet.
Planking was soon replaced by owling.
After the super bowl by bradying.
The newest meme is pulling the
shirt out to look like boobs.
It's called faith hilling.
All around the world people are doing it.
Kids, adults, and even notable
celebrities are getting into the act.
But as faith hilling is
more and more popular,
the question is, who will be
the first to die doing it?
I have been sent here because you
children are playing with fire!
Faith hilling is nothing more
than a evolution of bradying.
From football quarterback
to football singer.
Please.
Bradying is to 2000 and lame.
I know what you think is
doing is new, hip and cool.
The truth is meming has
been around a long time.
We are going to watch a film strip now,
although it's a little dated
but it gets the point across.
For many young people today
taking pictures in silly poses
becomes a dangerous past time.
The latest meme has also
become the most deadly.
It's called tebowing.
This is Ryan and Barkley.
They're about to learn how
dangerous tebowing can be.
Here is a good place.
I'll do it right here.
I don't know, Ryan, you
sure this is a good idea.
Stop being a scaredy-cat it will just
take a second how could I get hurt.
Okay hold still.
What's that?
A train!
Ryan!
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Ryan!
Learn from me.
This sure is a nice car, Tommy.
Would you like to get a
picture of me tebowing in it.
Sure.
What is that.
My God it's coming.
God no!
No, no!
Tommy, did you get the picture.
Hold on.
Hurry, hurry!
Be careful up, there Pete.
Go on and take the picture.
These youths paid with
their lives for tebowing
when they posed for pictures
they should have remembered
there are only three approved memes, peace
signs, bunny ears and fake winners.
Maybe you think this doesn't apply to you,
maybe you think your memes are safe.
Maybe you're watching this in the future
and teabowing has been
replace by some other meme.
Well, if you are watching
this in the future,
if you are get off your flying
cellphone scooters and think.
Just remember.
Use the approved poses if
you want to be a memer.
Peace signs, bunny ears, and fake wieners.
Oh, God. That was boring.
So, what do you want to do now?
There is the nice French cafe downtown.
Maybe we should get some faith
hilling pictures there.
That's a good idea.
What, you mean you guys still plan on
faith hilling after what we just saw?
Butters, faith hilling
defines our generation.
Count me out.
You're gonna give up on faith
hilling just like that, butters?
How could you?
I'm scared.
Did you see today's newspaper?
Why would we look at a newspaper, retard?
You made the front page.
Really?
Dude, we are on the front page.
Yes.
Can we get a different pose, please.
What's it say, what's it say?
It says...
Oh, no.
It says faith hilling is now
all like 2000 and late.
What?
Let me see that.
How can that be?
Already?
Public reaction was the stunt pulled off
by five elementary school students
wasn't not only dangerous and disruptive
but also completely passe.
How can we be passe?
We're only in 4th grade.
"Faith hilling is pretty stale" said
Republican candidate Newt Gingrich.
If they had crashed the debate by taylor
swifting that would of been impressive.
Taylor swifting?
What the fuck is that?
That's all it is?
You pull down your pants and wipe your
butt on the ground like an old dog.
But that's stupid.
How can that replace faith hilling.
It doesn't even make any sense.
I can't believe people take
the time to do this garbage.
This has to be stopped, you guys.
Okay. Hold it there. Okay.
That's good, don't move.
How is this? This good?
Yep, that's great.
These will be good.
What are you doing?
Faith hilling.
Why don't you get the fuck out of here?
Oh God. Faith hilling is so February 2012.
Saying something is so 2000
and anything is so 2009,
you stupid ass wipe.
Come on guys. It's not worth it.
We can do our taylor
swifting somewhere else.
Knock it off!
Why don't you make me.
Yesterday afternoon four kids went to
the hospital for injuries resulting
from meming in front of a local cafe.
Faith hilling, taylor swifting.
These are things that will get you killed!
That's a loaded .38.
How many pf you think it's a smart idea
to put a loaded .38 on a 9-year-old's desk.
If safety doesn't matter
go ahead, pick the gun up.
That's okay. I think...
Pick the gun up!
You might as well. Swifting and hilling
is like playing with a loaded gun.
Do you all understand my point?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Now put the gun in your mouth.
Hey. You're following plankers and teabowers,
so put a loaded gun in your mouth!
Do it!
Everybody take a good look.
This is what you're doing every
time you play with Internet memes.
You're playing roulette with your lives!
Professor Lamont, we need to talk.
I will be right back.
You're an expert on memes,
Professor Lamont.
Yes, what is this about?
We need your expertise.
Have you heard of another species,
meming on the Internet?
Another species?
What are you talking about?
We were hoping you could
help us understand this.
Cats have started to put pictures
of themselves on the Internet
with bread around their heads.
Kat breading is what it's called.
It's an odd thing to do, we thought
would you explain it to us.
They're evolving.
Cats are evolving.
Sorry?
There are two ways a species evolves.
Physically from genes and
culturally from memes.
Just like genes, memes
replicate, mutate and adapt.
We're having a hard time
following you here.
Look.
In the 70s there was fonzing.
Which replaced the outdated mustaching.
The 60s cultural ideas were passed
on by everybody poodle-fisting.
Even that evolved from people
ass wedging in the 40s.
Even before photographs
humans memed for portraits.
All the way back to the Egyptians who had
pictures painted of themselves donkey ticking.
You are saying cats are showing signs of
evolution with their Kat breading meme?
If they're putting slices of bread
on their heads and taking pictures
they're proving to be almost
as intelligent as we are.
Mister kitty, you want to explain this?
Why are you putting pictures on the
Internet with bread around your face?
This is a bad kitty, bad.
You're taking the idea of faith
hilling and making it stupid.
Bad kitty.
Bad Mr. kitty.
No more meming.
Come on, guys.
Bad mister kitty.
I'm glad we took care of that.
Ya, what do you want to do now?
I thought of faith hilling at
the place they do AA meeting.
That's a cool idea
what's the matter, Kenny?
I don't know.
What seems point less?
Hey, faith hilling is not
out of style alright?
No, no, no!
These stupid fads are only that, okay?
We can't give in to this crap.
Don't give up on faith
hilling, Kenny.
Don't you give up on her.
Two Boulder children died today while
oh long johnsoning in a battling cage.
Oh long johnsonning is of
course the latest Internet meme
which involves putting
oneself in a risky situation
and see how many times you can say
old long Johnson on video
before getting out of the way.
You ready, you ready?
I'm recording, go.
Oh long Johnson.
Oh long --
Larry.
This latest Internet meme is shocking.
But most shocking is the person who started
the meme isn't a person at all
but a cat who seems to have
no record for peoples safety.
Oh long Johnson.
The cat is awaiting trial for its
part in the teenager's death.
Oh long Johnson.
Yeah, that's good.
Now go back the other way.
Oh long Johnson, oh long --
Dude, what's going on?
Oh, hey, guys.
How's it going?
We thought you were
meeting us at Cartman's.
What are you doing here taylor swifting?
He's not taylor swifting,
that's old stuff.
Yeah, now you're doing to see how many
times you can say oh long Johnson.
I thought just, you know, try it out.
Remember when we heard about that pollack
with one testicle in the revolutionary war?
What's his name?
Benedict Arnold.
Oh guys. You need to realize that
faith hilling is over, okay?
You can pretend all you want,
but it's not coming back.
Kenny.
If you guys want to keep faith hilling
I'm sure people are still doing
it at the old folks home.
You will like this, Kenny.
Pull down your pants.
You guys are sellouts.
Come on.
You're freaking sellouts!
What are you doing?
When you play with memes
you're playing with fire.
Oh long Johnson.
Oh, very funny.
People are dying out
there. Is that what you want?
Oh long --
You cats want a war?
That's what you're going to get!
Oh oh oh.
Long ago there was tebowing
which evolved into faith hilling.
The latest meming craze, swift
johnsoning, may have it's rival
a brand new meme, where people videotape
themselves wearing trench coats
and talking about the dangers of meming.
They call it "reporting".
They say it's a dangerous
and potentially fatal.
Oh, oh long Johnson.
Oh long Johnson.
Ya, ya, that's cool.
Bring it out some more.
Ya, freeze. There.
What are those boys doing, daddy?
I think they're faith hilling, Bobby.
It's a little before your time.
How droll.
Get a couple facing the other way.
Ya, good idea.
You kids faith hilling
in front of my clinic?
I have a couple of patients that
could use a good time machine.
Get it?
Go back to the 90s!
We have to face it, Cartman.
I know.
I know Cal.
I thought it was going to last.
I guess the only thing that
doesn't change in life
is that things change.
***.
It wasn't like faith
hilling was that great.
I mean --
No, no.
It was kind of stupid really.
It's good it became something else.
We will have a blast
doing the new stuff.
Household cats have evolved
into a species as intelligent as humans.
Will this mean war between
our two life forms?
In an attempt to try to communicate
with the leader of cats,
experts have sent in the
ambassador of people.
Hello.
Oh long John.
Meow, meow.
Long Johnson.
Oh long Johnson.
Oh long Johnson--
Oh -- oh don piano.
Oh lala.
Oh long Johnson.
Don piano.
I'm not sure but I think it said war
between our species is inevitable
and evolution cannot be
stopped and cats will rise.
It said we cannot coexist and
then said oh don piano and then
and then something about seeing the streets of human
cities running red with the blood of their children.
Okay, that's good, a little higher.
I will go left to right.
Good.
Awesome.
Whenever you're ready.
No, kitty, you have to be quiet.
No kitty!
That's a bad kitty!
Wow, what's this?
What you been living under a rock?
This is the new meme, cat
taylor swift reporting.
Alright, go Cartman.
Taylor swift is dangerous.
Taylor swift is dangerous!
That's pretty cool.
That's cool.
It's awesome.
Super awesome.
We got it down, guys.
Think we're ready for the big times.
Shut up, kitty!
With the inevitable species war looming,
our country's brightest
leaders have come together
to debate and reason with
the ambassador of cats.
It's called putty-whistling.
And the question on everyone's mind...
Who will be the first
person to die from it?
I ran for president four years ago.
This is the position I
described when I ran...
If you want to be in
the -- I believe --
How big of a scale of change
do we want in Washington.
Oh long Johnson.
I hope --
I have five sons, five daughters
in law, sixteen grand children.
It's not the most attractive
thing to go out and say
it took me ten or twelve years
to figure out it was wrong.
Oh, long Johnson.
Fox trot standing by. Position outlook.
Fox trot, let's ***.
Standing by in three seconds.
Two, one. Go Cartman.
Less do this.
Cartman?
Go, Cartman.
Come on, dude. Hurry.
No.
No!
I won't do it.
I won't do it, you hear me!
I'm better than this.
To hell with you, Mr. kitty.
You're a bad kitty!
Bad kitty!
It's time somebody stood up
and did the right thing.
Ya, do it, Cartman.
♪ Alright ♪♪♪
♪ what do you do
♪ get out your camera and a booby or two
♪ we got to get serious --
have you ever seen faith hilling so good?
♪ come on everybody,
it's faith hilling time
♪ where are you
♪ this is the only meming I'll ever do
Oh long Johnson.
♪ I'm faith hilling until the day I die
And so in the face of war a
little boy reminds us all what
being human really means.
The message is unclear.
It doesn't matter as long as you give
the audience a song, celebrity bashing,
and republican hopeful
dancing around with boobies.
It's called pandering and all
over the country people are --
Oh long Johnson...
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net